

# CONTACT

- (+57) 300 322 3023
- kcomtdaniel@gmail.com
- https://co.linkedin.com/in/daniel -kcomt-frontend-developer
- https://portfolio-git-maindansaround.vercel.app

#### LANGUAGES

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Typescript

# FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES

- ReactJS
- Bootstrap
- Tailwind

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Asertive communication
- Team work
- · Problem solving mindset

#### **EDUCATION**

 Cum Laude in Social Communication

Universidad Monteávila 2012-2017

# Daniel Kcomt

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a passionate and adaptable professional who enjoys creating amazing user experiences and tackling technical challenges. I have taught myself frontend development using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and ReactJS, one of the most popular frameworks in the industry. I have more than six months of experience developing with ReactJS and using tools like Chrome DevTools to debug and optimize my code.

I also have skills in communication, radio and TV production, audiovisual specialization, and project management. I have a professional working proficiency in English and can use systems like Notion, HubSpot, Go High Level and Slack. I am open-minded, detail-oriented, responsible, and confident. I can work independently or in a team, meet deadlines, and learn from others.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Freelance Web Developer

2023 (Current)

Developed Personal Projects such as https://thexo.encolados.com using React. Website building for clients.

Tech Support

On The Fuze 2022-2023

Client training and support performed KPI analysis and optimized Landing Pages using GoHighLevel and Hubspot.

Freelance Web Developer

2020-2022

Created Landing Pages and Websites for individuals using Wordpress. Filmed and edited videos and executed marketing strategies.

VR Specialist

Uberflug Tech Marketing 2018-2020

Virtual Reality project management, leader of a 4-person work team. Photographer and developer of 360° virtual tours. Wordpress Content manager.